Guide to the Behind the Veil: Documenting African-American Life in the Jim Crow South Records, 1940-1997 and undated, bulk 1993-1997 RL.00170
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Electronic records - associated diskettes, 1991-1997; 1; 761 items
  - Disks, 1 (Box 7, Box 8)
    - Bullock, Lester - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0025)
    - Butterfield, G.K. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0026)
    - Campbell, Sarah - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0027)
    - Canty, John - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0028)
    - Canty, Mary - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0029)
    - Cappie, Herbert - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0030)
    - Cappie, Irene - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0030)
    - Carter, Dorcas - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0031)
    - Cheri, Emmett - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0032)
    - Childs, William - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0033)
    - Cross, Blondale Clady - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0034)
    - Daise, Kathleen - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0035)
    - Dave, Peter - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0036)
    - Davis, Price - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0037)
    - Dixie, A.I. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0038)
    - Dixie, Laura Mae and Samuel Lee - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0038)
    - Delaine, Marguirite - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0039)
    - Donaldson, Henry - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0040)
    - Donaldson, Laura - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0040)
    - Ely, Vermelle - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0041)
    - Flowers, Aurie Bell - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0042)
    - Forney, Myrtle - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0043)
    - Fort, Marie - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0044)
    - Gamble, Edward - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0045)
    - Gavin, Annie - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0046)
    - Gibson, O.C. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0047)
    - Gilmore, Sidney Jr. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0048)
    - Grant, Ernest - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0049)
    - Grant, Matthew - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0050)
    - Griffin, Lovie Mae - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0051)
    - Griffin, Robert - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0052)
    - Harrell, Willie - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0053)
    - Henderson, Ernest - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0054)
    - Hendrick, Lola - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0055)
    - Monroe, Irene - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0055)
    - Patton, William C. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0055)
    - Hinton, Catherine - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0056)
    - Holloway, George - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0057)
    - Hooten, Henry and Lillian - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0058)
    - Howard, Sallie Mae - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0059)
    - Jackson, Ruthie Lee - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0060)
    - James, Herman - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0061)
    - Jefferson, Harrietta - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0062)
    - Johnson, Harvey Jr. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0063)
    - Johnson, Mandie - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0064)
    - Johnson, Ruth - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0065)
    - Jones, Amy - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0066)
    - Jones, Ira Lee - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0067)
    - Jones, Otha B. Strong - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0068)
    - Jones, Wilhelmina - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0069)
    - Kirby, Anna - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0070)
    - Kirby, Money - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0070)
    - Knatt, Clement and Wille Mae - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0071)
    - Legree, Joseph - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0072)
    - Lewis, Charles - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0073)
    - Lewis, James and Marion - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0074)
    - Linyear, William - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0075)
    - Lucas, Julia - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0076)
    - Lucas, Maurice - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0077)
    - Lyons, Theresa - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0078)
    - Matthews, David - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0079)
    - McCrae, Aaron - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0080)
    - Middleton, Richard Webster - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0081)
    - Levy, Moses - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0082)
    - McCray, Josephine - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0082)
    - Nelson, Margaret - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0083)
    - Butler, B.O. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0084)
    - Nelson, Margaret - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0084)
    - Nesbit, Louise - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0085)
    - Page, Mildred - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0086)
    - Parker, Florida Lucille - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0087)
    - Pearson, Ferdinand - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0088)
    - Pearson, Frank - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0089)
    - Pitts, Anna - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0090)
    - Plummer, Vera - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0091)
    - Pointer, Ann - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0092)
    - Poole, Lorene C. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0093)
    - Poole, Lorene - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0094)
    - Cavers, Walter - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0095)
    - Reed, Willie - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0096)
    - Thompson, Ralph - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0097)
    - Adams, Wilhelminia - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0098)
    - Robinson, Violet - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0098)
    - Thompson, Jean - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0098)
    - Brickers, Alease - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0099)
    - Brown, John W. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0099)
    - Cherry, Olivia - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0099)
    - Blue, Ila - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0100)
    - Lyons, Theresa - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0100)
    - Alexander, Essie - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0101)
    - Bays, Georgia - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0101)
    - Chism, Tolbert - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0102)
    - Davis, Blanche - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0102)
    - Dennis, Dora - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0102)
    - Coker, William - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0103)
    - Edmonds, Marian - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0103)
    - Clayborn, Arthur - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0104)
    - Davis, Arnette - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0104)
    - Davis, William - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0104)
    - Davis, William Earl and Arnette - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0104)
    - Cooper, Barbara - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0105)
    - Cooper, John - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0105)
    - Hunt, Edgar - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0105)
    - Archie, Johnnie - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0106)
    - Brown, George L. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0106)
    - Clarke, Juanita - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0106)
    - Davidson, Geraldine - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0106)
    - Branchcomb, Flossie - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0107)
    - Linyear, William - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0107)
    - Wyatt, George - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0107)
    - Fisher, John - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0108)
    - Gratton, Charles - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0108)
    - Federick, Booker T - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0109)
    - Livingston, Daisy - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0109)
    - Georgia, Robert - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0110)
    - Smith, Abraham - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0110)
    - Howard, Helen - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0111)
    - Malone, William Thomas - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0111)
    - Rolling, Susie - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0112)
    - Taylor, Julia - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0112)
    - White, Bernice - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0112)
    - Fitts, Howard - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0113)
    - Quigless, Milton - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0113)
    - Searles, Arthur - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0113)
    - Ware, Elizabeth - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0113)
    - White, Nathaniel - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0113)
    - Aaron, Delores - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0114)
    - Aaron, Delores - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0115)
    - Adams, Wilhelminia - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0116)
    - Robinson, Violet - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0116)
    - Thompson, Jean - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0116)
    - Alexander, Essie - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0117)
    - Andrews, Malachia - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0118)
    - Andrews, Malachia - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0119)
    - Archie, Johnnie - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0120)
    - Attmore, Arlestus - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0121)
    - Bays, Georgia - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0122)
    - Borders, Florence - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0123)
    - Boucree, John H. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0124)
    - Bethune, Thelma - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0125)
    - Bouise, Louise M. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0126)
    - Blue, Ila - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0127)
    - Boyd, Leroy 1983 - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0128)
    - Boyd, Leroy - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0129)
    - Branch, Lanetha J. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0130)
    - Branchcomb, Flossie - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0131)
    - Brickers, Alease - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0132)
    - Browne, Corrine - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0133)
    - Bryant, Eddie - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0134)
    - Bryant, Artelia - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0135)
    - Butler, Willie P. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0136)
    - Bullock, Lester - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0137)
    - Butler, B.O. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0138)
    - Butterfield, G.K. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0139)
    - Caitone, Beverly A. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0140)
    - Caitone, Beverly A. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0141)
    - Campbell, Sarah - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0142)
    - Canty, John - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0143)
    - Canty, Mary - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0144)
    - Cappie, Herbert - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0145)
    - Carr, Peter - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0146)
    - Cavers, Walter - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0147)
    - Cheri, Emmett - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0148)
    - Cherry, Olivia - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0149)
    - Carter, Dorcas - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0150)
    - Childs, William - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0151)
    - Chism, Tolbert - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0152)
    - Clarke, Juanita - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0153)
    - Clayborn, Arthur - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0154)
    - Davis, Arnette - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0154)
    - Davis, William - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0154)
    - Davis, William Earl and Arnette - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0154)
    - Cross, Blondale Clady - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0155)
    - Daise, Kathleen - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0156)
    - Davis, Blanche - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0157)
    - Davis, Price - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0158)
    - Davillier, Brenda Bozant - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0159)
    - Dave, Peter - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0160)
    - Delaine, Marguirite - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0161)
    - Dennis, Dora - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0162)
    - Dixie, A.I. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0163)
    - Dixie, Laura Mae and Samuel Lee - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0163)
    - Dixie, A.I. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0164)
    - Dixie, Laura Mae and Samuel Lee - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0164)
    - Donaldson, Henry - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0165)
    - Donaldson, Laura - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0165)
    - Dulin, Mary - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0166)
    - Eaves, Elcie - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0167)
    - Ely, Vermelle - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0168)
    - Federick, Booker T - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0169)
    - Federick, Booker T - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0170)
    - Johnson, Harvey Jr. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0170)
    - Livingston, Daisy - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0170)
    - Fisher, John - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0171)
    - Flowers, Aurie Bell - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0172)
    - Forney, Myrtle - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0173)
    - Fort, Marie - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0174)
    - Gamble, Edward - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0175)
    - Gavin, Annie - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0176)
    - Georgia, Robert - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0177)
    - Smith, Abraham - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0177)
    - Gibson, O.C. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0178)
    - Gilmore, Sidney Jr. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0179)
    - Grant, Ernest - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0180)
    - Grant, Matthew - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0181)
    - Gratton, Charles - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0182)
    - Griffin, Lovie Mae - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0183)
    - Griffin, Robert - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0184)
    - Griffin, Robert - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0185)
    - Harrell, Willie - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0186)
    - Harris, Mable - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0187)
    - Hayslett, Elnora - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0188)
    - Henderson, Ernest - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0189)
    - Hendrick, Lola - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0190)
    - Hinton, Catherine - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-Fl3-0191)
    - Holloway, George - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0192)
    - Hooten, Henry and Lillian - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0193)
    - Howard, Helen - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0194)
    - Jackson, Ruthie Lee - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0195)
    - James, Herman - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0196)
    - Johnson, Harvey Jr. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0197)
    - Johnson, Jessie - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0198)
    - Johnson, Mandie - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0199)
    - Johnson, Ruth - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0200)
    - Jones, Amy - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0201)
    - Jones, Ira Lee - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0202)
    - Jones, Wilhelmina - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0203)
    - Knatt, Clement - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0204)
    - Kirby, Anna - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0205)
    - Kirby, Money - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0205)
    - Legree, Joseph - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0206)
    - Levy, Moses - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0207)
    - Lewis, Charles - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0208)
    - Lewis, James and Marion - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0209)
    - Livingston, Daisy - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0210)
    - Lucas, Willie Ann - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0211)
    - Lucas, Julia - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0212)
    - Lyons, Theresa - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0213)
    - Lyons, Theresa - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0214)
    - Malone, William Thomas - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0215)
    - McCrae, Aaron - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0216)
    - McCray, Josephine - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0217)
    - Middleton, Richard Webster - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0218)
    - Mitchell, Alma - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0219)
    - Mitchell, Cleaster - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0220)
    - Monroe, Irene - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0221)
    - Nelson, Margaret - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0222)
    - Nesbit, Louise - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0223)
    - Page, Mildred - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0224)
    - Parker, Florida Lucille - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0225)
    - Patton, William C. - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0226)
    - Pearson, Ferdinand - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0227)
    - Pitts, Anna - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0228)
    - Plummer, Vera - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0229)
    - Poole, Lorene - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0230)
    - Poole, Lorene - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0231)
    - Porter, Celestyne - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0232)
    - Richburg, Joseph - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0233)
    - Rivera, Alexander - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0234)
    - Rogers, Margaret - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0235)
    - Sanders, Gertrude - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0236)
    - Sanders, Gertrude - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0237)
    - Scarborough, George - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0238)
    - Scott, Jasper - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0239)
    - Scott, Louise - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0239)
    - Sherrod, Shirley - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0240)
    - Forest, Earl - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0241)
    - Sims, Constant - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0241)
    - Small, Henry - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0242)
    - Smith, Lillian Quick - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0243)
    - Smith, Lillie - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0244)
    - Bronson, Bernice - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0245)
    - Reynolds, Pamela - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0245)
    - Smith, L., Bronson, Reynolds - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0245)
    - Smith, Lillie - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0245)
    - Spencer, Robert - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0246)
    - Stewart, Ada Mae - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0247)
    - Studivant, Lenora - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0248)
    - Stewart, Ada Mae - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0249)
    - Jones, Otha B. Strong - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0250)
    - Swain, Ernest - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0251)
    - Swain, Ernest - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0252)
    - Taylor, Lovell - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0253)
    - Taylor, Lovell - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0254)
    - Wilson, Alberta - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0254)
    - Thompson, Ralph - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0255)
    - Miller, Taylor - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0256)
    - Smith, Alfred James - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0257)
    - Hooten, Henry and Lillian - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0258)
    - Tillery, Roy - 3.5" floppy disk, undated (Box 7, Disk RL00170-FL3-0259)